telugucinema.com 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy | telugucinema.com

The Privacy Policy provided below is with respect to our use and protection of any personal information you provide to us through the Telugucinema.com website.

Telugucinema.com is fully committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.

We do not collect or save any personal information. We do not place cookies on the computers of visitors to our site.

We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason. We do not maintain any databases storing any personal information about our visitors.

Since we do not maintain any personal information about our visitors, we will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about this site.

**Aggregate Information**

Telugucinema.com uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is used to enable us to improve and expand the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site.

We do not provide any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site.

The information provided by you shall be used by us to:

  * To provide you the most user-friendly experience which is safe, smooth and customized 
  * Improve and customize our services and content on the website.

**Advertising**

Telugucinema.com uses a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to [tcwebsite2013@gmail.com](https://accounts.google.com/SignOutOptions?hl=en&continue=https://www.google.com/preferences%3Fprev%3Dhttps://myaccount.google.com/u/1/privacy%26authuser%3D1 " tcwebsite2013@gmail.com")
